<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>automato.farm</title>
    <link>http://www.automato.farm/</link>
    <description>Recent content on automato.farm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 14:19:05 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.automato.farm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/09_swipeofdisdain/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 14:19:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/09_swipeofdisdain/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/11_tommaso/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 14:19:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/11_tommaso/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screen To Kilos</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/10_screentokilo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 13:20:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/10_screentokilo/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chips and Tails Workshop</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/06chipsandtails/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 13:18:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/06chipsandtails/</guid>
      <description>With objects that learn about our homes and environments or need to be taught about routines and habits, the way we interact with devices and machines will more and more start to look like the one we have with pets.
The relationship we have with Roombas, drones, cameras and thermostats might become closer to the one we have with dogs, cats, and birds. What products and services could be sold in a shop where pets are not only animals?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>piccioni!</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/07_piccioni/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Apr 2017 13:16:05 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/07_piccioni/</guid>
      <description> Piccioni #wip #threejs #blender
A post shared by Lorenzo Romagnoli (@10r3n20) on Mar 20, 2017 at 7:54am PDT
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gestures for AR in mobile VR</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/05_vrgestures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 11:05:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/05_vrgestures/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/05_realvr_saurabh_02/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Apr 2017 11:04:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/05_realvr_saurabh_02/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ethical autonomous algorithms</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/04_ethical-autonomous-algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Mar 2017 12:48:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/04_ethical-autonomous-algorithms/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>vitra</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/03_vitratwitter_01/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Mar 2017 14:19:11 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/03_vitratwitter_01/</guid>
      <description>Political plugs, ethical fan and training dust are all at #hellorobot @VDM_News !!! In a goooood questioning section... pic.twitter.com/bgGWVf09No
&amp;mdash; automato (@automato_farm) February 24, 2017  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domesticating Intelligence</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/01_domesticating-intelligence/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2017 12:48:25 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/01_domesticating-intelligence/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Year 0</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/00_welcome/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Mar 2017 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/experiments/00_welcome/</guid>
      <description>We launched finally a new website as a way to actually start to make automato.farm somehow less fictional and to put our work in shape and to create a space where we can also share our group and personal explorations beyond the work that we do. You will see all the weird little experiments that we do. From code snippets and awful wires mash ups and from lenghty articles to short stories.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>traiNNing cards</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/trainning_cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/trainning_cards/</guid>
      <description>Recently we hear a lot about Machine Learning, Deep Learning, and Neural Networks as being a revolutionary way for computers and machines in general to sense and recognize the world around them. Security cameras, home robots and other “intelligent” machines will have to recognize not only us but objects, pets and other inhabitants of our life with a training process that is hidden and done digitally through a generic set of images gathered from the web.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White Box</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/white_box/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Nov 2016 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/white_box/</guid>
      <description>The white Box is a new concept for a home control system that would be “transparently smart” to its user. In collaboration with Casa Jasmina, the first open-source smart home, we asked ourselves how “smart” can a home be? What kind of smartness are we talking about? Is technology in service of the user or is it becoming the controller of the user?
If you want to make your home “smart”, most solutions in the market come in form of a black box that takes care of everything for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>aboutPage</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2016 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/about/</guid>
      <description>automato.farm consists of Simone Rebaudengo, Matthieu Cherubini, Saurabh Datta and Lorenzo Romagnoli. We combine our pasts in computer science, product design and electrical engineering to work on the fringes of product and interaction design. Our work focuses on exploring the next evolution of what interaction design might mean. Bridging and blurring physical and digital interfaces, digging deeper into algorithms and behaviors of products, translating complex black boxes into interfaces and using connectivity and intelligence as new materials to be shaped.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>politics of power</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/politics_of_power/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2016 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/politics_of_power/</guid>
      <description>With a growing number of networked and autonomous objects as well as the outbreak of fields such as « the IoT », communication protocols used by connected products are increasingly important as they act as the network’s backbone. Since the end product is « black-boxed » to the user, we often assume that all nodes of a network are equal. But is it?
For example, in a home, two appliances in the same network must be working at the same time, but because of a power shortage, they cannot run in parallel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ethical things</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/ethical_thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2015 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/ethical_thing/</guid>
      <description>Due to fast-developing technology and its endless promises, autonomous systems are heading increasingly towards complex algorithms aimed at solving situations requiring some form of moral reasoning. Autonomous vehicles and lethal battlefield robots are good examples of such products due to the tremendous complexity of their tasks that they must carry out.
When it comes to discussion around the ethics of machines, the focus is often put on extreme examples (such as the above mentioned projects) where human life and death are involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teacher of algorithms</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/teach_algorithms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2015 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/teach_algorithms/</guid>
      <description>We think of smart/learning objects as yet not finished entities that can evolve their behaviors by observing, reading and interpreting our habits. They train their algorithms based on deep learning or similar ways to constantly adapt and refine their decisions.
But what if things are not that good at learning after all without some help?
What if in a near future, i could just get a person to train my products better as i do with pets?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ethical autonomous vehicles</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/ethical_autonomous_vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2014 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/ethical_autonomous_vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Many car manufacturers are projecting that by 2025 most cars will operate on driveless systems. While it is valid to think that our roads will be safer as autonomous vehicles replace traditional cars, the unpredictability of real-life situations that involve the complexities of moral and ethical reasoning complicate this assumption.
How can such systems be designed to accommodate the complicatedness of moral and ethical thought processes, especially when human lives are involved?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>