<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ethics on automato.farm</title>
    <link>http://www.automato.farm/tags/ethics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ethics on automato.farm</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2015 11:04:14 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.automato.farm/tags/ethics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ethical things</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/ethical_thing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Oct 2015 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/ethical_thing/</guid>
      <description>Due to fast-developing technology and its endless promises, autonomous systems are heading increasingly towards complex algorithms aimed at solving situations requiring some form of moral reasoning. Autonomous vehicles and lethal battlefield robots are good examples of such products due to the tremendous complexity of their tasks that they must carry out.
When it comes to discussion around the ethics of machines, the focus is often put on extreme examples (such as the above mentioned projects) where human life and death are involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ethical autonomous vehicles</title>
      <link>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/ethical_autonomous_vehicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2014 11:04:14 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.automato.farm/portfolio/ethical_autonomous_vehicles/</guid>
      <description>Many car manufacturers are projecting that by 2025 most cars will operate on driveless systems. While it is valid to think that our roads will be safer as autonomous vehicles replace traditional cars, the unpredictability of real-life situations that involve the complexities of moral and ethical reasoning complicate this assumption.
How can such systems be designed to accommodate the complicatedness of moral and ethical thought processes, especially when human lives are involved?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>